Kerem ÇALIŞKAN

Software Engineer

kerem.caliskan@yahoo.com

You can reach my portfolio inhere.

https://keremcaliskann.github.io/

SUMMARY

I am Software Engineer specializing as a Unity Developer with 3+ years of experience in mobile game development. I am proficient in C#, with a track record of contributing to all phases of game development, from design to deployment.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Game Development: 3+ years of experience in Unity using C#
- Game Publishing: Experience in testing, quality assurance, and deployment
- Version Control: Git and GitHub
- Additional Skills: UI/UX design, Animation, Level Design, Blender knowlage

EXPERIENCE

Game Developer, Toon Games

08/2023 - Present

- Actively participated in game design and development processes.
- Developed game mechanics and features using Unity.
- Participated in the game publishing process, including testing, quality assurance, and deployment.

Game Developer, Lecten

10/2021 - 08/2023

- Worked as a full-time game developer on multiple projects.
- Developed hyper-casual games for various mobile devices using Unity.
- Designed and implemented user interfaces, animations, and levels.

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering, Düzce University

2016 - 2023

REFERENCES

Mehmet ŞAKAR, Founder at Lecten

mehmet@lecten.com